日本語(日本在住者向け) English(for Japan residents) 日本語(海外在住者向け) English Français Deutsch Italiano Español(ES) Español(MX) Português(PT) Português(BR) Nederlands Ελληνικά Русский язык Svenska Türkçe Bahasa Indonesian العربية 한국어 简体中文 繁體中文

Privacy Policy
==============

Konami Digital Entertainment Co., Ltd. (“Konami,” or “we,” or similar) is a company incorporated in Japan with its headquarters at 1-11-1, Ginza, Chuo-ku, Tokyo, 104-0061 Japan. Konami recognizes the importance of our customer’s privacy (“you” or “your” or similar) and Konami handles your information (“Information”) in compliance with the applicable personal information protection law and in accordance with the following policy.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any services or products for which we have a separate, individual policy for the handling of Information. Otherwise, by using our services or products, you authorize us to collect, store, access, use and transfer your Information as described in this Privacy Policy and our [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html).

### 〈Contents〉

Information Collection
----------------------

Konami collects Information as set forth in the [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html).  
Our website uses cookies and other technologies for various purposes, including to distinguish you from other users. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our website, and display advertisements which are relevant to your interests. For detailed information, please read [the Notice for Cookies and Other Technologies](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/cookie_notice.html).

Information Use
---------------

Konami uses collected Information for the purposes specified in the [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html).

Information Disclosure
----------------------

We generally do not provide Information to any other third parties, except in cases where you have given consent; in cases set forth in the Information Handling Policy; in cases where the Information is to be disclosed in connection with an organizational restructuring or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock, including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings (in which case your Information will be one of the assets which is transferred between Konami Group companies, as defined below, for the purpose of any such restructuring, or may be disclosed and/or transferred to a prospective or actual purchaser of all or any part of our business); in cases where Konami is required to disclose the Information by law (including laws outside your country of residence); or in cases where disclosure is requested by a judicial, administrative or other government authorities (including an authorities outside your country of residence).  
  
We may also share Information as we believe necessary or appropriate: (1) to enforce our terms and conditions; (2) to protect our operations, rights, privacy, safety or property and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (3) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.  
  
Konami shares Information, for the purposes specified in the [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html), with members of the Konami Group (i.e., companies in which KONAMI GROUP CORPORATION has a direct or indirect stake, specifically, those listed in https://www.konami.com/corporate/en/subsidiaries/). In such cases, Konami Group companies that receive Information will use and manage the Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html). KONAMI GROUP CORPORATION is in charge of sharing of the Information among members of the Konami Group.  
  
Konami may from time to time have the service providers handle the Information we collect from you to achieve the purposes specified in the [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html). Our service providers may be the advertising and data analysis service providers.

Cross-Border Transfer
---------------------

Konami may from time to time store and process Information collected from you on servers located in countries outside your country of residence, even when we store and process the Information ourselves. In such case, your Information may be handled in accordance with law which may differ from those of your country. By using our products and services, you consent to such transfer of your Information.

Access Requests
---------------

If you would like to access, or you wish Konami to correct, delete, or stop using Information collected from you, please make your request in accordance with the procedures described in the [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html).  
Please note, however, that if the owner of the Information in question cannot be identified, or due to other circumstances, we may not be able to comply with your request. Furthermore, if you request that Konami delete or stop using Information needed to provide our services, we may no longer be able to provide you with services.  
If you would like to receive a copy of the Information we hold about you, please note that an administration fee may be applicable.

Your California Privacy Rights
------------------------------

If you are a California resident, you have the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, If you request such information, please email us to https://www.konami.com/games/inquiry/privacy/en/ with “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line.

Information Security
--------------------

Konami seeks to use appropriate and reasonable security measures to protect your Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us at the contact information provided in the [Information Handling Policy](https://legal.konami.com/games/privacy/view/en/information_handling_policy.html).

Retention Period
----------------

We will retain your Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

Children
--------

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

Changes to this Policy
----------------------

From time to time, we may make changes to this Privacy Policy. These changes will take effect when published on this website, and your use of our products and services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.  

**Revision History:**  
September 5, 2019  
October 25, 2016
